const decks = [
  {
    category: "Simple Past",
    decks: {
      easy: [
        {
          question: "say",
          answer: "said",
        },
        {
          question: "make",
          answer: "made",
        },
        {
          question: "go",
          answer: "went",
        },
        {
          question: "take",
          answer: "took",
        },
        {
          question: "come",
          answer: "came",
        },
        {
          question: "see",
          answer: "saw",
        },
        {
          question: "know",
          answer: "knew",
        },
        {
          question: "get",
          answer: "got",
        },
        {
          question: "give",
          answer: "gave",
        },
        {
          question: "find",
          answer: "found",
        },
        {
          question: "think",
          answer: "thought",
        },
        {
          question: "tell",
          answer: "told",
        },
        {
          question: "become",
          answer: "became",
        },
        {
          question: "show",
          answer: "showed",
        },
        {
          question: "leave",
          answer: "left",
        },
      ],
      medium: [
        {
          question: "feel",
          answer: "felt",
        },
        {
          question: "put",
          answer: "put",
        },
        {
          question: "bring",
          answer: "brought",
        },
        {
          question: "begin",
          answer: "began",
        },
        {
          question: "keep",
          answer: "kept",
        },
        {
          question: "hold",
          answer: "held",
        },
        {
          question: "write",
          answer: "wrote",
        },
        {
          question: "stand",
          answer: "stood",
        },
        {
          question: "hear",
          answer: "heard",
        },
        {
          question: "let",
          answer: "let",
        },
        {
          question: "mean",
          answer: "meant",
        },
        {
          question: "set",
          answer: "set",
        },
        {
          question: "meet",
          answer: "met",
        },
        {
          question: "run",
          answer: "ran",
        },
        {
          question: "pay",
          answer: "paid",
        },
      ],
      hard: [
        {
          question: "sit",
          answer: "sat",
        },
        {
          question: "speak",
          answer: "spoke",
        },
        {
          question: "lie",
          answer: "lay",
        },
        {
          question: "lead",
          answer: "led",
        },
        {
          question: "read",
          answer: "read",
        },
        {
          question: "grow",
          answer: "grew",
        },
        {
          question: "lose",
          answer: "lost",
        },
        {
          question: "fall",
          answer: "fell",
        },
        {
          question: "send",
          answer: "sent",
        },
        {
          question: "build",
          answer: "built",
        },
        {
          question: "understand",
          answer: "understood",
        },
        {
          question: "draw",
          answer: "drew",
        },
        {
          question: "break",
          answer: "broke",
        },
        {
          question: "spend",
          answer: "spent",
        },
        {
          question: "cut",
          answer: "cut",
        },
        {
          question: "rise",
          answer: "rose",
        },
        {
          question: "drive",
          answer: "drove",
        },
        {
          question: "buy",
          answer: "bought",
        },
        {
          question: "wear",
          answer: "wore",
        },
        {
          question: "choose",
          answer: "chose",
        },
      ],
    },
  },
  {
    category: "Past Participle",
    decks: {
      easy: [
        {
          question: "say",
          answer: "said",
        },
        {
          question: "make",
          answer: "made",
        },
        {
          question: "go",
          answer: "gone",
        },
        {
          question: "take",
          answer: "taken",
        },
        {
          question: "come",
          answer: "come",
        },
        {
          question: "see",
          answer: "seen",
        },
        {
          question: "know",
          answer: "known",
        },
        {
          question: "get",
          answer: "got/gotten (US)",
        },
        {
          question: "give",
          answer: "given",
        },
        {
          question: "find",
          answer: "found",
        },
        {
          question: "think",
          answer: "thought",
        },
        {
          question: "tell",
          answer: "told",
        },
        {
          question: "become",
          answer: "become",
        },
        {
          question: "show",
          answer: "shown",
        },
        {
          question: "leave",
          answer: "left",
        },
      ],
      medium: [
        {
          question: "feel",
          answer: "felt",
        },
        {
          question: "put",
          answer: "put",
        },
        {
          question: "bring",
          answer: "brought",
        },
        {
          question: "begin",
          answer: "begun",
        },
        {
          question: "keep",
          answer: "kept",
        },
        {
          question: "hold",
          answer: "held",
        },
        {
          question: "write",
          answer: "written",
        },
        {
          question: "stand",
          answer: "stood",
        },
        {
          question: "hear",
          answer: "heard",
        },
        {
          question: "let",
          answer: "let",
        },
        {
          question: "mean",
          answer: "meant",
        },
        {
          question: "set",
          answer: "set",
        },
        {
          question: "meet",
          answer: "met",
        },
        {
          question: "run",
          answer: "run",
        },
        {
          question: "pay",
          answer: "paid",
        },
      ],
      hard: [
        {
          question: "sit",
          answer: "sat",
        },
        {
          question: "speak",
          answer: "spoken",
        },
        {
          question: "lie",
          answer: "lain",
        },
        {
          question: "lead",
          answer: "led",
        },
        {
          question: "read",
          answer: "read",
        },
        {
          question: "grow",
          answer: "grown",
        },
        {
          question: "lose",
          answer: "lost",
        },
        {
          question: "fall",
          answer: "fallen",
        },
        {
          question: "send",
          answer: "sent",
        },
        {
          question: "build",
          answer: "built",
        },
        {
          question: "understand",
          answer: "understood",
        },
        {
          question: "draw",
          answer: "drawn",
        },
        {
          question: "break",
          answer: "broken",
        },
        {
          question: "spend",
          answer: "spent",
        },
        {
          question: "cut",
          answer: "cut",
        },
        {
          question: "rise",
          answer: "risen",
        },
        {
          question: "drive",
          answer: "driven",
        },
        {
          question: "buy",
          answer: "bought",
        },
        {
          question: "wear",
          answer: "worn",
        },
        {
          question: "choose",
          answer: "chosen",
        },
      ],
    },
  },
];

export default decks;
